facade yeah let the pixels glow let the pixels glow these words are truth in
drag painted wrongs the never-lack who does he think he is they tied better aim
your curses right
I'm precedented to commercial break, thanks to that loser that uh
talked about illegal harassment. This person is telling people to open my door and come on in
my house um asking for scrap metal and stuff so um you can go fuck himself as a zoned dick.
I love her, I don't know, maybe we're on the verge of something, and then we just want to, like, of course ruin it, but, you know, that person...
Oh, Bader's drunk? Oh, Bader's drunk and live again? Tell Bader to come here, and, um, I'll dance for him again, he can be a mod.
I was in Bader's chat today with the speedo on, oh my god, and he was like, dance for me, and I was like, okay.
I think I'm actually thinking I'm looking okay. I'm looking like better. I think I look a little healthier. Don't worry a little bit
I'm happy with my progress and my house is cleaner. I have like a lot cooler stuff
Let me fix my
But if someone wants to come up, well
Let me see how do I use?
There
and I blend in. And there. I love this picture though. I did this one today. It's a hookah.
It's love hurt me. And we want to relax. I am because it's like, I'm not like stressed about it
because it's like, you know, the worst has pretty much happened. And so it's like,
plus I have my backup plan, like I have my website almost ready. It's like a little bit slow slower
It's getting there. It's getting there. And I believe in myself
I
Know I did have someone that I really do care about a lot like that is a big supporter of the show
That was like, well, you know what? I don't like like the cult aspect of it. She's like, I don't think I want
She's like, I don't see you as like this religious leader. I was like, I
Think honey, it's the fish taco prophecy. It's like it's a little bit of a
Sat high. It's like a little bit of satire. It's like, I don't know. I don't know. I think some people might take it too seriously
I'm not here to tell anybody to like that. It's not an actual it's not like it like one of the bad cults
I'm not like and I like
Tell people to like do bad things and expect them to do I mean it's like I want people to be leaders and stuff like that
I don't know make sense. The whole thing is I just want people to like have a laugh and maybe it's like it looks a little bit
You know cool and interesting for some people. I'm also really into that kind of the aesthetic and
studied so much of secret society's luminosity. And now I have my own little
society, right? Even if it is like the highest level of teaching is returning into fish tacos.
Right? I just, now I just gave away the whole like plot, right? But it's okay. I still think it's
better than Scientology's story. Anyway. But I am streaming on kick and then the kick is
and dot com, and then it's over there.
It's a cult of good, not a cult of bad, exactly.
And it's also like not exposed,
it's not like trying to like control people's mind.
It's basically a culture.
And it's like, you know, and Psyche is not even just me.
Psyche is actually this butterfly goddess
from, you know, there's a beautiful myth
about Cupid and Psyche.
She was Cupid's wife,
but she had to go through a lot of shit because
She was so beautiful people started worshiping her instead of like Venus or Aphrodite and so Venus sent her son Cupid to like
Basically go go shoot an arrow at her so she'd fall in love with a monster
But then he accidentally pricked himself a little bit and then
He fell in love with her and she and he had porter report some stuff on her so she fell in love with him
I don't know. It was it was a big thing. I hate we've got it back. Let me see. I just want to make sure it's not a big dick
Holy fuck dude, what just happened man? Oh, it's just I think I think it's I think that's what Bronzeberg wishes
He had in his pants, but that was him. He did that. Yeah, that was him standing there
I must have been that no that was definitely wasn't him. I think it was just Tony
It was a big dude. You won't believe what happened after you shut the stream down
Fucking it was me. You me and Jamie Rose backstage, right? You're a freak off. No, hold on hold on
You me you me leaves. It's just me and Jamie Rose. Oh
Son her fucking camera goes on and your fucking giant hairy bush is fucking staring me right in the face. Oh
It was fucking like a jungle it looked like fucking Vietnam when I was in Vietnam
Well, I thought the VC were gonna jump out at any minute
Jamie, did that happen? Jamie, there's Bush. Okay. Well, God, he's gonna come up and say it didn't happen, but it happened
I don't know. Is this a true story? I'm not sure. I got pictures. You want to see? Oh, no
He has pictures Jamie that's the worst person to like do that in front of
I mean, I I think God he has pictures of me in this in a speedo with like leg to be on my head from like no no no no no no
I didn't take any pictures. Oh, thank God. Well, you do have you know the speedo pictures of me. No
Easy's got all those pictures easy has that hope but he's got a fucking library that shit
Vader wanted me to strip for him today. Yeah. Yeah, he showed his true colors, man
We knew he was kind of gay for years, but he proved it tonight
Yeah, but then I went back on a stream and he was like yelling at everybody and like
He kept saying uh psyche get on my pole get on my pole. What the fuck?
And I was like, where is it and I kept trying to like I was gonna try to hop on it, but
When he can't find I couldn't find it
I had a pole in my American flag speedo. It's called the flag pole. Who's this in the background?
Who's this exotic green?
Lilith and Scorpio writing a wolf. Oh
No, the green one. Oh the green one. That's okay. So you remember you said Kali. So this is one of
It's a avatar of Kali named Matangi
Matangi and she's the goddess of wisdom kind of similar to Saraswati, but she's like
More of an outcast like and also she like accepts leftovers and like she's she's a goddess of leftovers and stuff like that and of
Speech and of the subconscious and she's beautiful green. Hey, we look at this special guest here tonight. Let's welcome our special guest
One of Psyche's beauties.
Hello.
Please say Psyche, I didn't say, I didn't say anything mean to you, because you said twice,
you said thanks, means me too.
Oh, I wasn't mad about you. I wasn't mad about you about anything. I was just saying that you know
Christine hates me because of what you said, but I'm not mad at you at all about it. It's Christine's fault. I'm not I'm sorry
I didn't mean to say anything. I think he was so interested. I didn't say anything bad about you.
I don't care if it's me or if it's you
Why don't you say hi before you get into anything?
I mean Chris or I'm sorry
Hi!
If you say, I'm the problem, but you never even say what's wrong, no, you always say I'm
the problem.
I don't say you're the problem.
I love you.
I never said that.
I just said that.
Hey!
Christine's mad at me because you said that
She always said I'm the problem, but she has a lot of things that she doesn't know
She doesn't have a family that she doesn't follow
Sounds like she's saying
A bunch of fucking family no her family hates her her nephew's hater her fucking no they don't want any part
In their family and she tries to ruin people's lives and that's what christine is
She's a nasty dirty person and I hope karma gets like I have somebody
I
Listen to my comradery, please right now right now listen to me. Okay?
This bitch has been trying to come at me for years, right?
like
That God come on. She's talking. Don't please stop farting. I know because they're not gonna respect me
This is exactly what I'm saying. Hey, you know you know Gotti. He's just a jokester. Come on
Do you want me to drop off? I'll drop off
He's trying to make Joni laugh in the chat because Joni likes fart jokes. I know but Joni is
You know doesn't mean be a crack or a bunch
We love Jody. We love Jody.
She just got it mixed up in the wrong situation.
I don't know if yours, I think yours is a game of different.
Let's not talk about other people, really.
Let's all have a hug.
But listen, what do you think, how do you, how would you feel if somebody is always saying the bad, like...
I know Chris. I'm true things about you.
I played that song where it's like...
Everyone loves you because it's like, you know what I'm fucking saying like they're they're on island
They're on an island
Vita is on an island and I can't wait to go to her fucking city to beat her fucking basin
Oh my gosh, that's all I'm saying. Oh, so you want to do violence?
Yes, I go to violence and I've always rolled to violence
Okay
I know you're a fighter because it's like, you know, yes, listen, I roll it out. I fight it out and I fucking get it out
I don't have it in my blood anymore. Okay
Well, I don't mean to upset you. I'm sorry if I don't have it
Okay, you know what? It doesn't really matter what you have
Anyways, cuz you know then you are a fucking you grew up as a camp on
What? You are a legit tampon. You grew up to be a fucking wiper. Did you say I'm a tampon? Yes
You have to be a wiper
That's my crystal you're being very very very very weird
Not tampon. I'm a human being. Yeah, you're a tampon faggot. Ah
How dare you
dare you
Talked to me like that. I'm the host of the psyche
Well, you know what honestly, I fucking adore the fucking shit out of you. Yeah, I was like
But I'm saying the way that like you like you
Or I think I'm sorry, Crystal. I know but I was busy, you know, I love you though, you know
I'm a total mess you you're you see it. I am a tampon probably I'm I should I should have just been you know a
Clot of blood left on the toilet, but you know what I survived now. I'm a very you did you did survive
You can always that's what I'm saying like these things that
that girl like she's trying to ruin my reputation and my uh thing uh and i have it to god yes
and she's doing it to other uh other people we're gonna get this all figured out
fascinating we have to get this sorted out but i have so much more money than her
she's so broke i'm just a money issue for every penny she has
Well, they're talking bad about are we talking about we still talk about this. I'm gonna give it to you. Oh
boy
Well, you know
Christine clapped me off of the panel which I'm inside
Christine doesn't deserve to have a single
Her family didn't even give her $1.00. You know how crazy that bitch is that where they didn't give her one cent
Ever no never. No, she's okay. Can I interrupt your family?
Can I interrupt for a job crystal crystal crystal crystal crystal crystal crystal can I interrupt yeah?
I got this bitch crystal listen crystal can I interrupt for one second?
Sorry, I
Just just for a second. Just for a second. I really I'm sorry. No, okay. Just interrupt for one second. Just one second
I I really care here. I want to interrupt just for one second. That's all
That you that's the last guy who that's the last guy who crossed me psyche across me
the
I got their names. I got this motherfucking name. I'm gonna get them locked up. There's no playing games no more
We're getting you locked up. This is a no, I guess. Okay. Well, you know what? I mean, I don't know
It sounds like a case for like no, they're being mean. Okay. I'm sick of being abused. Okay. Well, I hear you
I don't know what he likes to be. Hey crystal abuse is a choice
Know when I'm sick of it guess what happens
Christine gets her head kicked in by 90 year old man
What?
What did this happen yeah at her fucking at her thing she's got to get her head kicked in
Oh, or fucking throw down the fucking stairs
You're all goons are you fucking stupid?
Yes, she's bad
No, no somebody you've got to come out them hardcore and it's about to be about three ninety year olds
Oh my god. Well, you know what? I gotta take a piss. I'll see you guys
That's like a very old gang. Okay. Well, God, you had to leave. Okay guys. I
Guess I guess Christine shouldn't come at people because she's about to lose her life. Okay. That's ours
Okay, oh you think that Christine can walk down the fucking flight of stairs three times with
With people that hate her as much as they do
Well, I would
Keep fucking threatening 90 fucking 90 year old people I think our nine year people need to start threatening back
No, but they're almost kind of on the way out aren't they? No, but we need to start threatening for them. Okay?
Okay, I don't I'm not sure what's going on at that hospital, but I'm gonna give Christine the benefit of the doubt that
Yeah, Christine needs to get to the psycho
Award of it all
Okay
psycho award
Yeah, the psycho word the crazy, you know that he has got the double
duty
dynamics of
Did you see
Did you like your video that I made for you I played it earlier tonight, you know, oh, I didn't see it but man
I know I seen I seen that you made you know how much that makes me feel like I
Love it. Oh, you love it. Okay kid
I
Feel so much more powerful again
You know these people don't understand that I have a way more power than they ever have in their tiny little toes
I think beautiful beautiful women are the powerful force in the world. I really do believe that, you know, you definitely qualify, right?
100% yeah
So I'm not I'm not gonna doubt your I'm not gonna doubt your power or anything. I'm not I'm not gonna mess with you
I guarantee you, I'm more powerful than, like, let's not.
Like, I don't want to, that's like so ugly to say it too.
Oh my, yes, I'm better, you know what I mean?
Someone said, I'm picture Jimmy Rizzo.
Oh, is he 90 years old?
Let's see, you're going to ban who?
Oh, are you okay, Jimmy?
Are you sick?
My god, that's not good ammonia. Have you been Chris like you've been feeling well? Oh
Fucking phenomenal
I'm good. He's done. He sounds up full of energy tonight
No, you know, I feel like it's very funny
That people come to me a group
And it makes me almost like my family is very powerful. They don't even know me
They actually have never but they may have seen me on video. You know what I mean? They have may have seen my
fucking
My pod throw my fucking ability my pod throw my of my abilities my fucking family my fucking beautiful
Fucking, but they didn't see themselves
You know what I'm saying, huh?
Yeah, I mean people really need to get in touch with their true selves. I believe I do believe that I think we're
Like a lot of people like get mad at me because they don't even have that ability to have like what I have right
Well, yeah, so we should we should um, you know all encouraged other not try to be competing against each other, right?
and why
Why is Christine so fucking saying like I have all these
Like I always tell my mom I tell my mom
I just wanted everybody to know what she was doing
Because I really want people to go after her now. I know I I I never had nobody do this, but
Actually have somebody out to kill me now. Oh
Yeah, I never even felt like this like in my entire life
Yeah, my entire life you should have some protection or like, you know, at least like, you know security system
So I wanted yes, I wanted to say it just even though it does sound crazy
It doesn't I'm not saying that I sound sane
It's okay. I don't believe this world is sandal. Who's who is saying in this world? You know, what a sanity
I don't know, but they can say whatever because they were attacking me for the same shit because I was friends with Charlie as well
You know
Well, I wish we could have some peace. I mean, but just Christine's has been so mean to me and she's like
I she said I would she said in the chat. She said I were crazy tonight
She's like, oh a second his mental illness is showing and I said well her leather face of showing and it's like
Her leather face is definitely showing. She is definitely a fucking mental case
She is like the craziest bitch. She has a no sense of life
Christine
Okay, and and we really need to make this known and I'm gonna make it known because she likes to make it known about me
So I'm gonna have to like put it at every platform like she does to me
Yep, that's not gonna be and we should write an AI song together about it
That may end up a producer.
Her name is Christine.
I'm gonna write this down a little bit.
She thinks she's so pretty.
She's a fat, but she's skinny.
She doesn't realize.
Well, you know what?
The people that can't,
they think people look like they're dogs.
She kind of looks like Fawzi, doesn't she?
Man, she told me that her animal. Okay. This is when she was really is on she's on drugs, dude
You know when I get drunk, I feel like I'm high on drugs. I don't even know I'm like I
Don't do I don't do drugs though. I swear to God, but she said that she was on drugs and her dog
I mean that she had a cat and that her cat
that she took in this cat from the street and
She found that the cat
Was getting the bird sick
Okay, she said she said that the cow was keeping in the bird section. Okay, and then
And this is where I get with the rabies thing because she said that the cat ended up having rabies, but it was her dog.
But she ended up getting everything fixed and then the dog ended up having rabies.
And that she wouldn't get the dog fixed because it was so old and it was her dog and it didn't matter.
But she was running around with her kids her nephews and nieces and then going to schools and then and then
Having all these people, but she's supposed to be nursing aid
And she was mad because she's like she's like, oh, I'm a nurse
She's like imagine it's like one of my one of my patients that eventually got you know hit by a bus or something
And they come in the hospital. They're gonna they're gonna think I'm gonna do something to them
I'm like, that's a very bad
And it's a very good well tell and we needed to well tell this and guess what she needs. Oh, sorry, sir
Speak your mind
No, you're very well tell sir
She is, she's very well like fucking threatening our lives and saying that her animal has a fucking weird disease and she's threatening me with her animal.
Well, I I hope Bosnian doesn't have any
Bosnian's a beautiful and animals are just innocence. And so we want to you know, hope Bosnian's okay
And you know, but this is what this bitch does. Have you not paid attention?
What you do their dogs are sick. Oh my gosh my fucking animal sick right now
My gosh feel sorry for me. I'm stupid. I have a sick animal. I fucking retarded
Okay, well, you know what let's like transmute some of this
Um energy into like something more positive. Oh my gosh. I'm so sorry. Can we please do that?
I'm pleased. Thank you for saying that and please
Song again, do you want to hear that song again? You like that song? Yes. I love it so much and people try to fucking hate me
I love you. Why can't I get love? Why can't they love me again?
This is a this is a crystal Marie song and I listen sir. They all love me until they get it. Okay
Well, I I mean, I don't I don't see who could not live because you're just I know I love you
I love you too, but they only love me because I
Will never I'm not like them. They're never gonna like they're never gonna love me. I
Sometimes feel a similar way, but okay, let me see if I have
Crystal Marie song
Where is it? Oh, it's so beautiful. Thank you so much. You know, but you don't like it either. You know, it doesn't really make you know that.
I love it. I love it so I played it earlier. I mean, it's like, I love it.
I know, but what you said after, you know, in the background was not very nice. And it was like, okay.
I just don't even know what I said. You just have to let me know because I don't remember saying anything bad about you.
Did I, I'm sorry, if I did, I do apologize.
I don't think I was mentioning,
I was just talking about Christine basically.
I haven't.
You were very mean to me.
I was mean to you, I'm so sorry,
Chris, I didn't mean to be mean to you, I love you.
I'm always so mean, everybody's so mean to me,
everybody just happens to.
Oh, don't cry, here, this is it, is this at home?
Is this, that's a ghost?
Yeah, oh, here's it, I found it.
No, I don't cut. I mean, I do have feelings and everything. I am a human. I am a one.
And I'm sorry that I'm upset.
I'm- I would- I'll die with no money.
I'm sure I'll die, uh, like they won't kill me, or no thanks.
I don't like that's what they want, you know, like, I don't believe it.
Show my soul.
You might be right
Talking about killing my entire soul. Oh my god, like the evaporating thing. I don't know what that means
Invaporating yes evaporating like killing me. Okay?
So guess what listen, but you don't even know what I have of gods dude
My gods are higher than her stupid fucking her fucking gods have nothing on my god
Her two gods are short and fucking fat and stupid and
Disgusting she worshiped oompa loompas and yes, and I try molesters. Oh my god. No, like herself. Yes
Yeah, that's a little too far it looks like
We don't we don't have proof about something. Let's just like yeah, I have it. I have it
Just a little bit I have it proof and we're gonna do it at one time, but see a man's gonna do it for me
So we're not gonna
Look he's reliable. I ain't gonna do it
I just really kind of want it to be a correctly because you know, we gotta let them right they
Beat you down and we're gonna let him be there
Okay, well
Let's play the rest of the song, okay? Let's play the rest of the song. It's so good.
Bye! Okay, thank you, sir.
No, I can't hear it. We're on different systems.
We're on different systems.
We're on different circumstances.
I can't hear you.
We're on different levels.
Fear not.
The way the crowd won't go, she's part oracle, part in the net myth, have the room scared, the rest subsist, her eyeliner sharp as a truth, I say it, and then we theory leaves the chat, and fed you, you laugh, but you're still tuned in, because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin.
I've had them, but they keep their people.
Hell, or you are.
You don't want to hit me.
You don't want to throw up the fuck away.
You don't know you're in a bad condition, by the way.
But you want to get killed, right off.
I see people are sick.
So sick.
What do you say Nick?
That looks like you are.
Bye bye. What happened?
I'm playing a video. Oh, I didn't see the video.
I'm playing back after.
That was basically it.
Yeah, so, okay, now that was a good little break.
So I didn't see it. I'm sorry. Well after the stream rewind and I'll also I'll I'm posting on my
On my page and I'll tag you in it. Do you have a page and stuff I can tag you?
I'll tag you in the song so you can have it forever. I really don't I have my original like just my Chris and Marie
This is the original. I don't fucking put on friends. Hey, guess what?
Christine is super pissed off because
The other chick, you know the other chick that she fucking hired to attack me said no, no
this bitch is
She said no, no this bitch is getting way too many people against me and she's crying every day
Yeah, I've I've I've I've said, you know crystal Marie is like because you remember you said you were joking about it
And I was like I was like I don't control it crystal Marie says and so but I mean she's mad at me
She's not mad at you. She's mad at me actually for letting you say it or something
Hey, do you know anything about about trafficking trafficking kids or that you meant goats, right?
Because a baby goat is a kid, right?
No, I did say that because she has a dog that
as rabies. Oh my god. I hope it's not policy. Well, she said that she and then I want my
people from the fellow 90 year old, I have a fellow 90 year old fucking goon. Okay, I
Offsters like remember there must be very old mobsters like you know, I got a 90 year old goon in her fucking area of fucking
fucking stupid ass
Don't be very reliable because it's like 90 year olds can't really like run around that fast
Well, listen listen to fuck it. That's what Christine is
She's 90
You said memories that she was very very old
Is she nine? Well, these people are her goons. So they're about to push her down this they can't wait to push you down the stairs
is what they said I
Wouldn't really be afraid of like a nine-year-old came like it to attack me
I would just kind of like get out of the way and like run lock the door or something
Yeah, they're pretty much ready to push her down the fucking stairs and tell her a story about
everybody else
Well, Christine, you better watch out for those 90-year-old goons, Christine.
You never trust, you know...
Yeah, she's got 90-year-old goons on her fucking back, bitch.
That is intense. I mean, it's like...
They're ready to push her down the fucking steps.
Yeah. Christine, fire these goons, Christine.
What is she, a mafia leader or something?
No, I got him.
Oh, you got him, okay.
Well, I got the goons. I hired the goons because I hate Christine so much so now
Now Christine is parents and her family
Okay her
Okay, I'll say one thing is that her siblings are really bad
Okay, her family or whatever or whatever. She's going off of her or whatnot
It's really really bad
Okay, and they're really really bad people by the way. They're like six
trafficker styled like
bad people her old family her old family like you can just Google it okay i don't i don't know i
i don't know i'm not sure i mean any christine could come up i don't i'm not using any last names
or anything but yeah no you can look up christine's the fucking her name is kelly oh careful no dox
So we it could be any it could be any Christian. I'm not so the Christine. We're not necessarily talking about no
It's the same one her like she is like tries to be a drug trafficker
But
She just tells on everybody but her but her like like she's like really bad
She's just telling on everybody like her her son. That's a piece of shit. That's like a drug trafficker and that like her
daughter-in-law that's
Got like 24 charges against her. Anyways, it doesn't matter in none of that drug trafficking traffic
You know matters because
We would never do that normal life. I would never let that shit is gross
She's a sick bitch. She's a disgusting whore
You know what it matters is that Christine thinks that we fucking roll
Disgusting like she does we don't
Well, if what you say is true then it's like she's involved in some very bad stuff
But I really I really am gonna pray for that. You know, she she changes her ways, you know
No, she's not gonna change her ways and guess what? I got a better ones there in New York
And that's gonna fuck her over
Her job and everything. Okay. Well
And her daughter's job. Thank you so much
Well, they want to do it to me. They keep doing it to me
They keep saying that I have multiple personalities and saying that I'm crazy and all these things and it's not true
And I just want to make sure that the Lord is
proper on this and
God's
Giving karma catches up with those bitches and they came up quicker than later and it normally does
Let's hope that yeah, I think I believe in karma and it's like you know people that do bad things bad things happen
You know Chris Christine said I was mentally ill tonight, and then I said she had she had a leather face
And so I thought I think we're even
I'm not mad at Christine, but she's mad, but she's not mad at you. She's mad at me. That's the problem
It's like because of what you said, but she's not mad at you. That's good
But now I think tonight after tonight she might be mad at you. Oh listen listen
She can never be mad at me because she thinks it's funny to me. She thinks it's okay to be mentally
It's okay to hurt the mentally challenge, right? And she says as far as her her mentally
maturity
She said her mentally maturity said it's okay to mentally
Beat up this bitch. It's that it's like hard averse mentality words like they said oh Aaron Carter's on drugs
So you he can like, you know, you can bully him and stuff like I people have said that
I just are you never done drugs those see the thing is I've never done drugs in my entire life
Yeah, well I experimented in college, you know with the
Like Adelix and stuff. Well, I I mean, I don't know if you want to call drugs
like
Smoking weed like a couple times
Nothing wrong with that
Yeah, I never even did weed. I never even did weed because it's just not a part of my
Thing alcohol and weed are not two things. You know what I mean, right?
Pills and weed are not two things right and nurses can sometimes get great drugs
You know they can get like the the pharmaceuticals on variety, right?
That's why those nurses end up on like heroin addicts like Christine
Christine is a heroin addict because she is
She's a different kind of
You know, I was just an alcohol person that drink maybe a couple times a
Well, yeah heroin is the very very strong joy. I mean that's what that's that girl and and her are on
Okay, but who's the girl? Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky, Sponky
Yeah, it doesn't really even mattered. Uh, you know, you know, it's so weird back then they try to do this whole thing to me
about four years ago with
with that
mentally ill guy
No hurt their friend
I'm not I'm at it was before my time, so I'm not sure who it was, but no you're mentally at their mentally ill fucking
That the the Spanish guy. Okay. Oh auto
No, not auto. Yeah, pretty diamonds
I am not sure who it is
Anybody have an idea? What's going on? So what's do you believe in goat trafficking? I'm
Well, you're not being very nice to me, and you're not
Reading the chat reading the chat, sweetie. I'm not trying to I just reading the chat
I swear captain you're not being very nice to me, and you're acting like I'm condescending you're being very
Yeah, they said captain is a captain content
No, it's not and it's fine. It's fine. It's fine that you're being condescending. I'm not being condescending. It's what I get.
Personality, I'm just like, I'm trying to be an interviewer and like, and not like, be disrespectful to anyone.
I'm trying to like, walk a fine line before.
Then when do I get respected?
I respect you. I respect you. I respect all women. I do respect you.
Then when do I ever get respected?
I love you. I respect you. Okay? Captain Crunch? Was it Captain Crunch?
The guy in the cereal box, was it him?
I don't think he was a real captain though, I'm not sure.
I like the berry, the crunch berry.
What are you eating? Do you have your candy bar?
Are you- are you- are you-
What's that for?
Chris, are you okay?
There's plenty there for it still. What's going on? Oh, is it cat food? Oh
Well that didn't go as planned
Okay, guys, if you have any information about the Spanish guy, I
Don't I just don't know it's a little bit
Yeah, it's a little bit like I'm not it's a little bit general a Spanish guy like
There could be a lot of people. There's literally like millions of Spanish people or maybe almost
Is there a billion? I'm not sure but it could be a lot of people if you have information about the Spanish guy
Contact with submarine, okay. Um, whoo, um anybody want to come up? Hey guys, um
Who wants to hang out? Hey, hey, I want to see Lola
Crystal come back up. I love you Chris. So I wasn't being condescending. It's just like you're you're you're
Telling me is a
Lot of interesting information. I just trying to sort through it. I mean, it's I'm just trying to like not
Cues anybody of me think because just because for Siemens saying saying oh, I like condone what you're saying
I mean, it's like I don't I think that she might be innocent. I think she might be I
Don't know better hiring 90 year old goons who are gonna end up pushing her
Or you're I don't know. It's seriously. I'm just confused crystal. You can confuse me
Good and dog had her psyche meow meow. Yeah, her love language crystals. Love language is
Conspiracy conspiracy theory, I think that's her love language
That's why I wrote that song about her, but it wasn't supposed to be like rude
I mean, gosh, she gets so mad at me sometimes. I don't
Make her mad
You might whoo anybody want to come up reasoning good morning reasoning
Um, yeah, I mean, it's like sometimes when people talk like that, it's like there's there's
something to it, but I just don't know.
Maybe it's like some kind of spiritual thing that's beyond me.
I just don't know.
Yeah, it could be psychic reasoning.
Right.
It could be like, it could be some kind of, you know, the spirit or something, it could
be a metaphor.
I don't fucking know.
Christine, please don't get mad.
I mean, sue me or something like that.
I mean, it's like, I just had her on my show.
Okay.
I don't control what comes out of her mouth, okay?
But she's beautiful, she's funny, she's cool,
and I respect her, okay?
And I will defend her if she ever gets,
you know, 90-year-old people coming after her.
Or anybody else, and if Chris Kay
and his white supremacist gang come after her,
I'm gonna suck all their dicks.
Did I say that out loud?
Oh my gosh.
What was yeah, she sounded like she was rifling through
Something yeah, and it sounded like there's like some kind of metal. I just don't know
Maybe it was a hopefully it wasn't kind of
self-defense
Or maybe it was just like, you know, oh, hey, what's up come up? Hey crystal. I love you crystal
So do you come back up to I'll put the link back up if anyone's come up
Maybe somebody else can like help me get to the bottom of this. I really I think we can I think we're making progress on this on the story
Crystal, I mean Christine you're welcome to come up and defend yourself
Christine never I like I don't want to be like bias like I want you to have your side of the story too
but Chris Christine you've been very mean to me and
And you say you don't watch the show, but then you know things that happen on the show
So obviously you're like giving information and you said oh well one of my mods is telling you
I knew that is you know, it's okay if Jamie is telling you everything that happens the shit. It's fine. I
Want you to be informed, but it's like just stop being mad at me. Okay, then I can like
Get a better place to like know what's going on to the picture. Okay, but you certainly
You know
You set off you set off crystals radar, but you know we are they're both crystal and christian very similar name. Here we go
Hello